Mr. Ming.
We found Ma Derong's place.
Where is it?
[Ambition Spanning Spring and Autumn]
In Heiqiao.
Okay.
Got it.
Thanks.
Clearly, this is all
food that kids eat.
Chang.
Have someone watch this place.
If he comes back,
follow him.
Make sure you don't alert him.
Okay.
Hello?
Mr. Ming, that old guy is finally back.
Alone?
Yeah.
Just him.
Is he still in Heiqiao?
He didn't stay long after coming back.
My men have been following him.
He went to Dianshan Pier first,
and now he's at a car scrapyard.
Dianshan?
Yeah, so I'm wondering
if he's trying to smuggle himself out?
Which car scrapyard?
Botong Shenglong.
The one on Yueping Road.
Have Hu keep an eye on him.
I'm heading over now.
Okay.
Ma Derong has been found.
[THE GUILTY]
[Episode 10]
As expected, you came.
Where's Shanshan?
Strange.
Go ask Xia Xue.
Ma Derong.
The grudges between us
have nothing to do with the child.
If it weren’t for Shanshan,
would you guys still be alive?
Every day you guys are alive
is because of Shanshan.
You're a murderer now too.
Would Shanshan be better off with you?
Mind your own business.
Give Shanshan back to Xia Xue.
I'll turn myself in.
You'll turn yourself in?
You'll go to the police and say
it was me, I killed Ma Ke!
And the police will just arrest you?
I have evidence to prove it was me.
So you really were the ones
who hid my son's remains?
I'll turn myself in.
Give Shanshan back to Xia Xue
and never bother them again.
Sure.
Why should I trust you?
You don't have to trust me.
I want to see what you're capable of.
Give me 3 days.
I'll turn myself in after 3 days.
Alright.
I'll wait for you.
I'll wait for you to go to jail.
Ma Derong really has Shanshan.
[Lin's Repairs]
But the smuggler at Dianshan Pier told me
that they'd been in contact.
Is he taking Shanshan out of the country?
What exactly is he planning?
I don't think he'll take Shanshan
out of the country.
He promised to give me 3 days.
I turn myself in,
he returns Shanshan to Xia Xue.
Turn yourself in?
But I still don't fully trust Ma Derong.
He could turn on us at any moment.
He just got out of prison.
Not many people can help him.
I'll go with you.
I'm going too.
You shouldn't go.
Go home.
Don't make the police suspicious.
Leave it to me.
Where do you think
he could be hiding the child?
He's been locked up for 10 years.
Who would still help him?
I sent someone to investigate.
To see who visited him
while he was locked up all these years.
Why don't we
give him Ma Ke's body?
Do you really think
that if you hand over the body,
he'll let Shanshan go?
Why do you trust Ma Derong so much?
What else can we do?
All these years,
if we weren't waiting
for Shanshan to turn 18,
we would've turned ourselves in long ago.
Lin Hua.
It's been so many years.
He's had the DV tape the whole time.
Why didn't he give it to the police?
Maybe he just wants us dead.
To avenge his son.
[Police]
[Hou Shanshan] [Biological father?]
Do you remember the name of the relative
who went with her?
His name is Hou Jun.
I'm not Shanshan's biological father.
[Hou Jun] [Married couple] [Xia Xue]
After investigation, we found that
Hou Jun used to be Ma Derong's secretary.
So him accompanying Xia Xue
to the hospital
was likely on Ma Derong's orders.
And Hou Jun's former boss,
Ma Derong,
was charged with multiple crimes
and sentenced to 10 years in prison.
He was released just half a month ago.
Before he went to prison,
all his assets were seized.
After his release 10 years later,
only a car shop
under his son's name, Ma Ke, remains.
We've already been there.
Nobody's running it
and it has been closed down.
We also found
Ma Derong's residence in Beishan Village.
But it was clear that
no one has been there for a long time.
What about DNA?
We found some hair
at his place and the car shop
that's been sent to the lab.
Boss.
Ma Derong can't be
the kid's father, right?
He's so old.
10 years ago, I handled a case
[Police Office Operating Procedures]
involving Lu Ming, Xia Xue, and Lin Hua
[Mediation Center]
fighting and brawling together.
The person they fought
was Ma Derong's son,
Ma Ke.
We were wrong.
We were really wrong.
It was a misunderstanding. Sorry.
So you're saying
the child's biological father
might be Ma Ke?
Eat up.
You're not eating?
I already ate.
Hello?
Mr. Ming. Hu found
Yao, who just got out of prison.
When he was in prison,
he was in the cell next to Ma Derong.
He said that during the holidays,
someone would always bring him things
and visit him.
What's his name?
Ma Derong calls him Old Kang.
Old Kang.
Got it.
Lin Hua,
stay here and keep watch.
I'm going to find this Old Kang.
Okay.
[Old Kang Rice Noodle Shop]
[Police]
Okay. Call me anytime if there's news.
Wen.
Ma Derong's
DNA
test results are back.
[DNA Test Report]
He and Hou Shanshan
share
a grandparent-grandchild relationship.
The DNA
similarity is 27%.
[DNA Test Report]
[DNA Matching Test Report]
Also, the DNA
under Wang Bingkun's fingernails
matches Ma Derong's perfectly.
There's one thing I don't get.
Why did Ma Derong kill Wang Bingkun
and take Hou Shanshan?
Could it be that after Ma Derong
got out of prison,
he wanted to take his granddaughter back,
so he ordered Wang Bingkun
to kidnap Hou Shanshan,
but then they had a conflict,
so he killed Wang Bingkun
and took his granddaughter away?
Hello?
Put Captain Qin on.
Ren Yi, go ahead.
Captain Qin, Qiao and I found that
Lu Ming wasn't just looking for Ma Derong.
Lu Ming was also looking for Wang Bingkun.
Wang Bingkun is a prime suspect
in Hou Shanshan's kidnapping case.
And Ma Derong is a prime suspect
in Wang Bingkun's murder.
Lu Ming is in such a hurry
to find them both.
He's definitely involved in this case.
Ren Yi, keep looking for Lu Ming.
Call me if there's any news.
Roger that.
Yang, keep following
the Ma Derong lead.
Go.
Okay.
Get ready and come with me
to another place.
Yes, ma'am.
Who are you looking for?
Municipal Criminal Police.
Where is Lu Ming?
You again, sir?
He's not here.
[Harmony Brings Prosperity]
We're very busy here at Sancheng.
If you want to talk business,
we're very...
Where is he?
Please, he's the boss.
I'm just an employee.
He doesn't need to report to me
where he goes, right?
Leaving now?
Take care. I won't see you out, sir!
Wen, Lu Ming isn't there.
I know.
I didn't see Lu Ming's car just now.
Then you made me...
If I didn't make you go upstairs,
how would they
send word?
Hello, Mr. Ming.
The police came to the office
looking for you just now.
Be careful.
I know what I'm doing.
Hello, Qiao.
I found Lu Ming's location.
He's moving east
near Yunhe Elementary School.
Yunhe Elementary School?
Wu,
have Ren Yi follow him.
Find out what Lu Ming is planning.
[Old Kang Rice Noodle Shop]
[Ma Derong] [Ma Ke] [Hou Shanshan]
Hello, Ren Yi.
Captain Qin, I found Lu Ming.
He's right near
Hebai Community.
Should I detain him?
Not for now.
Just follow him.
Don't spook him.
Stay in contact.
Roger that.
Boss.
Ren Yi, where is he now?
Zhangjia Intersection bus stop.
He stopped, but didn't get out.
Well,
are you absolutely sure
the person in the car is Lu Ming?
I can't see him right now.
There's a bus blocking my view.
You've probably been spotted.
That probably isn't Lu Ming
in the car either.
The bus moved.
I can see the car now.
Follow that car and see where he goes.
Got it. Following now.
I can't see him right now.
There's a bus blocking my view.
Bus...
[From Yitian Station
to Tianshan Road Intersection Station]
[Lianhua Village 1] [Lianhua Village 2]
[From Yitian Station
to Tianshan Road Intersection Station]
[Lianhua Village 3] [Dongsha Market]
[Dongsha Market Station]
[Zhangjia Road Station]
[Zhangjia Road]
[Haishou Island Pier Station]
[Shilianhua Village]
[Laoshi Station] [Chengnan Middle School]
[Hebai Community Station]
[Hebai Community]
Near Hebai Community.
Wu.
Let's go.
Let's look around Hebai Community.
Wen.
Lu Ming.
Why is he taking so long to eat?
He shook off Ren Yi, circled half the city
just to come back here for a meal?
Are you sure he's here to eat?
Eating isn't the point.
Wait a little longer.
[Old Kang Rice Noodle Shop]
Lu Ming!
Officer Qin, Officer Wu.
What brings you here?
By the way,
the porridge here is really good.
Drove halfway across the city
just to eat it?
How did you know?
Did you drive around too?
Now that you've had your fill,
we have a few questions for you.
Ask.
Why were you looking for Wang Bingkun?
Wang Bingkun owes us money.
I was collecting a debt.
How much does he owe you
for you to go to such lengths to find him?
Well...
We have our own methods.
What about Ma Derong?
Ma Derong?
You mean Ma Derong from the shipyard?
Isn't he in prison?
Lu Ming, don't play dumb with us.
No, I'm cooperating, aren't I?
Then we thank you for your cooperation.
Any more questions?
If not, I'm leaving.
Wen, are we just letting him go?
Keep following him.
Be careful.
Yes.
Go now.
Hello?
I'm sorry, Mr. Ma.
Something happened.
[One day ago]
Take care.
Come early tomorrow.
Okay.
Drive safe.
Old Kang, closing up so early?
I miss my grandson.
I'm going home to play with him.
Alright, I'm off.
Work's done.
Okay.
Xiaohu.
Grandpa.
It's so late, you're still not going home?
Still playing outside?
Come on, go home with Grandpa.
Let's go!
Old Kang!
Bought treats for your grandson again?
He loves them.
I'll just fix them up at home.
Take care.
Okay.
What's your name?
Kang Xiaohu.
Your grandpa runs
Kang's Porridge Shop, right?
Chang, go back to the office first.
[Wear a helmet when cycling,
get home safely]
Be careful not to give anything away.
Where is Lu Ming?
Please, he's the boss.
I'm just an employee.
Chang,
go to the bus stop on Zhangjia Road.
I can't see him right now.
There's a bus blocking my view.
You've probably been spotted.
[Hebai Community]
That probably isn't Lu Ming
in the car either.
[Hebai Community Station]
Boss, enjoy your meal.
Don't move.
If you want to know
where your grandson is, sit down.
Don't move.
Sit down.
Wen.
What do you want?
Where did Ma Derong hide Hou Shanshan?
What Shanshan?
I don't know.
Ma Derong was in for 10 years.
You visited him a lot, didn't you?
Calling you his most trusted person,
wouldn't be an exaggeration, right?
How about this.
Let's make a deal.
You tell me where Hou Shanshan is hidden,
and I'll tell you where your grandson is.
Things run a certain way on the streets.
I'll give you 20 seconds.
Why hasn't he finished eating yet?
Eating isn't the point.
Wait a little longer.
Chang.
I'll talk.
Xia Xue.
We've located Shanshan.
Go to Shatang Village right now.
The police are already onto Ma Derong.
We need to hurry.
Shanshan.
Mom!
Mom.
Mom, I missed you so much.
It's okay. Mom's here.
Mom's here.
Hello, Lu Ming.
I found Shanshan.
She's fine.
But I don't see Ma Derong here.
That's great.
Stay safe.
Yeah.
Lin Hua, Shanshan's been found.
How is it on your end?
Ma Derong still hasn't shown up.
Keep watching.
There are police here.
I can't go back for now.
Be careful.
Ma Derong is bound to make a move.
I'll keep an eye on him.
You protect yourself too.
Don't act rashly.
Okay. Wait for news.
Shanshan has been found.
Your grandson is home, too.
There are police at the door.
If you don't want to get caught,
wait half an hour before going back.
Officer Qin, Officer Wu.
What brings you here?
Grandpa!
Xiaohu!
For you.
Thank you, mister.
Hello?
I'm sorry, Mr. Ma.
I'm sorry.
Lu Ming used Xiaohu to threaten me.
He forced me to reveal
Shanshan's hiding place.
I didn't know he was bluffing.
I was worried about Xiaohu's safety,
so I...
That's not important.
Who was the person behind Wang Bingkun?
I won't let go of the things
that need to be investigated.
Shanshan!
Let Dad take a look.
You're not hurt, right?
Where did you find her?
I'll tell you when we get back.
Okay.
Shanshan, let's go home.
Mrs. Hou.
She's back.
You two, you two!
It's wonderful. My child is back!
Don't mention it.
I'm just glad she's been found.
She's been found.
Why don't we all go inside?
Let’s go in.
No.
Mrs. Hou, please come
to the Criminal Investigation Unit
to make a statement, okay?
Now?
Yes.
But the child just got back.
Look, she's been frightened.
Let her rest tonight.
We'll go first thing tomorrow, okay?
Mr. Hou, we understand how you feel.
After all, your child was just found.
But we hope you'll cooperate with us,
alright?
Yes, we understand. We get it.
Of course we-
Let's listen to the police.
Okay. Alright then.
[Police]
Let's go.
You're back.
[One-Stop Service Counter]
I'm sorry,
Mr. Hou, Mrs. Hou.
We made you come out when it's so late.
[Nanping Police Bureau]
I'll take them upstairs first.
Could you please wait here for a moment?
Sure.
You go ahead.
I'll wait for you here.
[One-Stop Service Counter]
Let's go upstairs first.
Okay.
Come here, Shanshan.
Come, let Mommy hold your hand.
Don't be afraid, Shanshan.
The reason auntie
asked you to come here today
is to ask you a few questions.
Just tell auntie whatever
you can remember, okay?
Mommy is right here with you.
You are safe.
You don't need to be afraid of anything.
Let's start from the day you went out
to walk Taotao,
okay?
That night,
I snuck out of the house.
Taotao!
I was taken by someone
and taken to a strange place.
Who is it?
What are you doing?
So that Grandpa
just saved you from the bad guy,
and never hurt you at all,
right?
Shanshan, think carefully.
Any detail you remember, you must tell us.
That way we can catch the bad guys sooner.
But Grandpa isn't a bad person.
Shanshan.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here to save you.
Don't be afraid. It's okay now.
It won't hurt anymore.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
Once we catch the bad guy,
we'll go home safely.
Okay?
Good girl.
Shanshan.
That's most of the questions, right?
So, Shanshan,
auntie's done asking questions for today.
Thank you.
You can go home with your mom now.
Excuse me, Mrs. Hou.
I just want to confirm something with you.
Was it Lu Ming
who helped you find Shanshan?
Yes.
Then I may have more questions later
and may need to speak with you again.
Okay.
Let's go. Give me your hand.
[Forensic Evidence Laboratory]
You're out. Let's go.
Let's go home.
They said
they have a few more questions for me.
More questions?
Why did you ask Lu Ming
to help find your child?
I thought
he might know more people.
I was really desperate to find my child,
so I wanted to try everything.
Then have you considered
why Ma Derong would go save Hou Shanshan?
Because
Ma Ke is Shanshan's biological father.
So when you gave birth
at Nanping Bo'ai International Hospital,
it was arranged by Ma Derong.
Who else could it be?
What about Wang Bingkun?
And Wang Bingkun?
I don't know him.
That's all for today's questions.
I'll contact you if there's anything else.
Thank you for your cooperation.